ez.no 2015-12-19

# Privacy policy - Home - eZ Publish Platform, CXM & CMS

At eZ Systems, your privacy is important to us. For that reason, we have adopted this Privacy Policy to explain our information gathering practices. This policy may change over time, so you should check back for updates. 

#### No Required Information

In general, you may visit our Web sites [www.ez.no ](http://www.ez.no/)or [share.ez.no](http://share.ez.no/) without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. eZ Systems collects domain information from your visit to customize and improve your experience on our Web site. 

eZ Systems’ Web site(s) may collect certain information from your visit, including the date and time of your access, the pages you have accessed, the name of the Internet Service Provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address by which you are accessing the Internet, and the Internet address from which you linked to our site, if applicable. We use this information to better understand how our Web site is being used so that we can improve its quality and make it more beneficial to our users. 

#### Personal Information

Certain areas of our Web site may request personal information. If you choose to provide this information, the information will be used to respond to your requests for particular information about us or from our site. We may also use the personal information you provide to us to send you additional information about us by e-mail. You may, at any time, opt-out of receiving future e-mail communications from us by following the instructions in the e-mail you receive. Please note that you might start receiving e-mail communication again if you subsequently submit personal information at this Web site. We do not share any personal information you choose to provide to us with any third party. 

#### Linked Sites

Our privacy policy only covers our Web sites at [www.ez.no](http://www.ez.no/) and [share.ez.no](http://share.ez.no/). Some areas of our Web site might contain links to third party sites. We do not control the linked sites and we are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest that you check the privacy policies of these sites before providing any personal information to them. 

#### Community Site

Our community site - located at [share.ez.no](http://share.ez.no/) \- may request personal details from you as part of your community profile. Any information you share is voluntary and might be accessible to other members of the community. Certain areas of the community are accessible to everyone.eZ Systems may terminate your community account if you engage in any practice that is, in eZ Systems' sole discretion, objectionable, unlawful, obscene, threatening or hateful, or that encourages conduct which would constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate any local, state, national or international law.
